Guide to the Turkish Photography Collection 1910-1990 AD.MC.007
AbuDhabi
- Two young women holding pocket books in front of a doorway. 8.4 x 13.2 cm, Monday, 18 November 1948; Unknown (Box 8, Folder 1)
  Books; Fashion Accessories; Gelatin Silver Prints; Photographic Prints; Turkey; Turkish Writing; Women
- A large mixed group of women and children in a house. 9.0 x 14.0 cm, Undated; Studio Foto Atlas, Istanbul, Turkey (Box 8, Folder 1)
  Children; Drinking; Eating; Gelatin Silver Prints; Istanbul, Turkey; Photographic Prints; Women
- A woman in a knee-length dress standing in front of an oasis of palm trees. 8.5 x 13.3 cm, Undated; Unknown (Box 8, Folder 1)
  Date palm; Gelatin Silver Prints; Photographic Prints; Trees; Turkey; Women
- Three sewing machine tables in an empty room. 9.2 x 13.9 cm, Undated; Unknown (Box 8, Folder 1)
  Gelatin Silver Prints; Machines; Photographic Prints; Sewing; Turkey
- A man in a suit, sitting in a flower patterned arm chair. 8.9 x 14.1 cm, Undated; Unknown (Box 8, Folder 1)
  Furnishings; Gelatin Silver Prints; Individual Portraits; Men; Photographic Prints; Suits; Turkey
- A man and woman leaning over a balcony, looking at the camera below. 8.8 x 13.9 cm, Undated; Unknown (Box 8, Folder 1)
  Balcony; Gelatin Silver Prints; Jewelry; Men; Photographic Prints; Turkey; Women
- An older woman with a covered head, sitting a table outside. 9.2 x 14.0 cm, Undated; Unknown (Box 8, Folder 1)
  Fashion Accessories; Furnishings; Gelatin Silver Prints; Head Covers; Photographic Prints; Restaurants; Turkey; Women
- A young girl with a uniform on, receiving an award with two men, one who is holding a microphone. 9.0 x 14.1 cm, Undated; Unknown (Box 8, Folder 1)
  Carpets; Gelatin Silver Prints; Girls; Men; Microphones; Photographic Prints; Schools; Turkey; Uniforms
- Two women in a room with a wood burning stove. 8.7 x 13.8 cm, Undated; Unknown (Box 8, Folder 2)
  Gelatin Silver Prints; Mirrors; Photographic Prints; Stoves; Turkey; Women
- A man standing behind the counter of a hardware store. 8.8 x 12.8 cm, Undated; Unknown (Box 8, Folder 2)
  Advertisements; Clocks & Watches; Gelatin Silver Prints; Men; Photographic Prints; Shopkeepers; Shops; Turkey; Unknown Locations
- An older woman sitting on a bed, eating and drinking. 9.1 x 13.9 cm, Undated; Unknown (Box 8, Folder 2)
  Beds; Drinking; Eating; Gelatin Silver Prints; Photographic Prints; Turkey; Women
- A family group of four women and three men. 9.1 x 13.7 cm, Undated; Unknown (Box 8, Folder 2)
  Gelatin Silver Prints; Head Covers; Men; Photographic Prints; Suits; Turkey; Women
- A group of seven men in pajamas, probably at a hospital. 9.0 x 13.9 cm, Undated; Unknown (Box 8, Folder 2)
  Gelatin Silver Prints; Group Portraits; Hospitals; Men; Pajamas; Photographic Prints; Turkey
- Four women and a man with two young girls wearing the same outfit. 9.1 x 14.0 cm, Undated; Unknown (Box 8, Folder 2)
  Children; Gelatin Silver Prints; Girls; Men; Photographic Prints; Stoves; Turkey; Women
- Three women and a man sitting in a living room drinking Coca-Cola. 8.3 x 12.4 cm, Undated; Unknown (Box 8, Folder 2)
  Cigarettes; Drinking; Family; Furnishings; Gelatin Silver Prints; Men; Photographic Prints; Turkey; Women
- Four women and a man standing out on a balcony/porch., Undated; Unknown (Box 8, Folder 2)
  Eye Glasses & Sunglasses; Gelatin Silver Prints; Men; Photographic Prints; Turkey; Women
- Three women, two men and small baby with a pacifier. 9.1 x 13.6 cm, Undated; Unknown (Box 8, Folder 2)
  Calenders; Children; Family Portraits; Gelatin Silver Prints; Men; Photographic Prints; Turkey; Women
- Ten men in suits standing on the steps of a building. 9.0 x 14.0 cm, Undated; Unknown (Box 8, Folder 2)
- Two men in suits with two women, sitting in front of some curtains. 8.9 x 11.6 cm, December 1966; Unknown (Box 8, Folder 3)
  Eye Glasses & Sunglasses; Gelatin Silver Prints; Jewelry; Men; Photographic Prints; Suits; Turkey; Women
- A man and a woman sitting at a restaurant table, with a young boy sitting on a bench nearby. 9.0 x 14.1 cm, Undated; Unknown (Box 8, Folder 3)
  Boys; Drinking; Eating; Gelatin Silver Prints; Men; Photographic Prints; Restaurants; Turkey; Women
- A man with his arm around an older woman. 9.0 x 13.8 cm, Undated; Unknown (Box 8, Folder 3)
  Clocks & Watches; Gelatin Silver Prints; Men; Photographic Prints; Turkey; Women
- A young girl with glasses, with her arm around a woman in bed. 8.9 x 13.7 cm, Undated; Unknown (Box 8, Folder 3)
  Beds; Eye Glasses & Sunglasses; Gelatin Silver Prints; Newspapers; Photographic Prints; Potted Plants; Turkey; Women
- Two young boys in sweaters with a young girl in the middle. 9.1 x 14.0 cm, Undated; Unknown (Box 8, Folder 3)
  Boys; Children; Gelatin Silver Prints; Girls; Photographic Prints; Turkey
- A young couple sitting at a table reading and smoking. Same couple from ref 1616. 8.7 x 13.5 cm, Undated; Unknown (Box 8, Folder 3)
  Couple; Gelatin Silver Prints; Painted Backdrops; Photographic Prints; Reading; Smoking; Studio Photography; Turkey
- A young couple sitting at a table reading and smoking. Same couple from ref1615. Duplicate photograph. 8.7 x 13.5 cm, Undated; Unknown (Box 8, Folder 3)
- A young couple, with a small child seated on the lap of the man. 14.0 x 8.9 cm, Undated; Unknown (Box 8, Folder 3)
  Children; Couple; Family Portraits; Gelatin Silver Prints; Photographic Prints; Turkey
- Three veterinarians operating on an animal. 8.8 x 14.0 cm, Undated; Unknown (Box 8, Folder 3)
  Animals; Gelatin Silver Prints; Medicine; Men; Photographic Prints; Surgery; Turkey; Veterinarians
- A large group of young men in military uniform, in the snow. 8.8 x 14.0 cm, Undated; Unknown (Box 8, Folder 3)
  Gelatin Silver Prints; Group Portraits; Men; Military; Photographic Prints; Snow; Turkey; Uniforms
- A young woman sitting on a chair, holding a brush. 13.9 x 8.9 cm, Undated; Unknown (Box 8, Folder 4)
- Young man wearing suit and tie and young woman wearing a three-button blouse. 8.7 x 13.7 cm, Undated; Studio Foto Sabah, Istanbul, Turkey (Box 8, Folder 4)
  Couple; Gelatin Silver Prints; Istanbul, Turkey; Men; Photographic Prints; Studio Photography; Women